Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Launch in:
Launch!
Autopilot
Cancellation Failure
Main Elevator
Emergency
Shut Down
To the person in my memory.
Midnight Highway Explosion — Terrorism?
Yuki
Snow
Preparing to Warp
Initiating Standby
Connected
Severed
Emergency Exit
Occupied
Save
Me
Activating
Episode 14
The Whisper of the Witch
Believe that
Only the future
Has the answer
No one knows
Memory only strikes at
The heart to find
The truth
Do not forget it…
Many stars lie beyond
The spiral of memory
Sparkling in what looks like
The light of memory